{
 "subject": "geography",
 "lesson": "l02",
 "grade": "c8",
 "quests": [
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Earth's atmosphere contains about percentage of nitrogen and oxygen.",
		"options": {
			"a": "78% and 21%",
			"b": "22% and 1%",
			"c": "21% and 0.97%",
			"d": "10% and 20%"
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "is generally defined as the average conditions of the weather of a place or a region.",
		"options": {
			"a": "earth",
			"b": "atmosphere",
			"c": "climate",
			"d": "sun"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "The earth receives energy from",
		"options": {
			"a": "current",
			"b": "electro magnetic radiation",
			"c": "waves",
			"d": "heat"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "Which one the following represents places with equal amount of rainfall",
		"options": {
			"a": "isotherm",
			"b": "isohel",
			"c": "isobar",
			"d": "isohytes"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "is used to measure the humidity.",
		"options": {
			"a": "anemometer",
			"b": "barometer",
			"c": "hygrometer",
			"d": "thermometer"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "Climate",
		"options": {
			"a": "Locating and Tracking Storms",
			"b": "Cyclone",
			"c": "Equal Snowfall",
			"d": "Long Term Changes"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "Isonif",
		"options": {
			"a": "Locating and Tracking Storms",
			"b": "Cyclone",
			"c": "Equal Snowfall",
			"d": "Long Term Changes"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "Hygrometer",
		"options": {
			"a": "Locating and Tracking Storms",
			"b": "humidity",
			"c": "Equal Snowfall",
			"d": "Long Term Changes"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "Radar",
		"options": {
			"a": "Locating and Tracking Storms",
			"b": "Cyclone",
			"c": "Equal Snowfall",
			"d": "Long Term Changes"
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "Low Pressure",
		"options": {
			"a": "Locating and Tracking Storms",
			"b": "Cyclone",
			"c": "Equal Snowfall",
			"d": "Long Term Changes"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "The atmosphere is a layer of gases surrounding the planet.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "The Scientific study of weather is called Climatology.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 13,
		"question": "Isohel refers equal sunshine.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 14,
		"question": "Humidity is calculated by Aneroid Barometer.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "b"
	}
  ]
}